▍2026 美网 男单第一轮
布云朝克特 6-2 6-1 6-1 霍达尔 · 赛后场上采访
You just defeated the number 12 seed
你刚刚击败了 12 号种子
in Rafael Jodar in straight sets
霍达尔 直落三盘
even through the slight rain delay.
中间还赶上了一次雨中断
What does this win mean to you?
这场胜利对你意味着什么？
Actually I was really lucky loser
其实我真的是个幸运落败者
so and yeah it
所以说
was a little bit tough you know is everything
是有点难 你知道 所有事
is on my side and then just rain
都站在我这边 然后下雨了
and a little bit stop and then make me think
中间停了一阵 让我有点乱想
a bit but you know we just do our job
但我们只是做好自己的事
very focused and then save the energy
保持专注 保存体力
and then ready to come back anytime.
随时准备回到场上
So I'm really happy for that.
所以我真的很开心
And then you know it looks looks like
而且你知道 这看起来
like very easy but for sure in my in my mind
好像很轻松 但在我心里
in my heart it's like many many emotions
其实是很多很多情绪
is very very very nervous actually.
真的非常非常紧张
Yeah.
是的
So many emotions
那么多情绪
because yesterday you just found out
因为你昨天才刚知道
that you were playing in the main draw
自己能打正赛
as a lucky loser.
以幸运落败者的身份
Where were you? Were you
你当时在哪呢？
on your couch watching a movie?
窝在沙发上看电影吗？
Were you packing your bags
还是在收拾行李
to leave New York?
准备离开纽约？
Where were you
你当时在哪
when you found out this news that you
听到这个消息的时候
would be playing in the main draw?
说你可以打正赛了
Yeah, actually you know
是的 其实
after I lost the last round
我输掉资格赛最后一轮之后
the qualies you know I'm super tired
你知道 我累坏了
and we take a day off
我们休息了一天
and then second day we supposed
第二天本来
to take a day off and I see few guys pull out
也想休息 但我看到有人退赛
and we make decision to come back
我们就决定回来
on court you know chill with my coach
回到场上 和我的教练
and my fitness coach
还有体能教练待着
and then you know we just spend all
我们就把所有时间
the time together and try to try
都待在一起 试着
to do some work you know in case I
做点训练 万一
have to play but I'm really lucky yesterday
真要上场呢 昨天我很幸运
they tell me I can play and you know I
他们告诉我可以打了
was every day I come 8:00 a.m.
我每天早上八点到
and then I go back home probably 8:00
大概晚上八点
p.m.
才回家
You know,
你知道
I was ready to die like zero energy.
我快累死了 完全没有力气
And yeah, when I heard I have I can play
而当我听到我能打的时候
with Lucky Loser, I feel like, wow,
以幸运落败者的身份 我心想 哇
I'm super excited.
我太兴奋了
You know, it doesn't matter 8 a.m.
你知道 早上八点也好
or 8:00 p.m. I can be here all day, 24 hours.
晚上八点也好 我能待 24 小时
I mean, yeah.
就是这样
Well, you just won your first Grand Slam win
你刚拿下大满贯正赛第一胜
and you're off to the second round.
而且晋级了第二轮
What do you want New York to know
你想让纽约知道你的哪一面
about you that they don't know
是他们
about you already?
还不知道的？
Actually I really love New York you know
其实我真的很爱纽约
I it's almost my favorite like grand slam
这几乎是我最喜欢的大满贯
because I make like
因为我
I played two years here
在这儿打过两年
and then I always I make both main draw
两次都进了正赛
and I didn't win any match
但一场都没赢过
and this year even I lost qualies
而今年我连资格赛都输了
and I play main draw again and I win.
却又进了正赛 而且赢了
So I mean I love here and then thanks
所以我爱这里 也谢谢
for the crowd everything everybody
现场的每一位观众
to come out to watch and support
来到这里看球 支持我
and hope see you next round.
希望下一轮再见
Well, anything can happen here
在美网 什么都可能发生
at the US Open and Bu,
而布云朝克特
you are headed to the second round.
你晋级第二轮了
New York, make some noise for
纽约 为他欢呼吧